

Stu Coston

2928 Palamino Drive Benton, AR 72015 385-288-0899 stu.coston@gmail.com

Profile

For the last 6 years I've worked as a project manager on \$2.3B worth of Government programs and a number of large scale construction projects. During this time, I fell in love with graphic design, digital marketing, and website development. I have been building brands, designing digital experiences, and doing digital marketing work on the side for businesses and start-ups for about 5 years but I'm ready to take it full-time. A creative designer at heart, my passion is catching consumer attention and creating an experience that entices them to take action.

Skills HTML

••••••

CSS

JavaScript / JQuery

•••••

WordPress

••••••

Photoshop

Adobe Creative Cloud

Work History

Program and Contracts Manager 2012-2017
United States Air Force

Front-End Developer and Copywriter 2014-2017
Freelance

Assistant Project Manager
2018-Present
CDI Contractors

Education

United States Air Force Academy 2008-2012
Bachelor of Science
Systems Engineering

Experience

Designer

Learned html, css, and js on nights and weekends in order to publish a quarterly online magazine for my family's vacations

Designed websites and graphics for bands, personal trainers, small businesses, churches, political candidates, and local organizations -- decreased average page load time by 40%, got two clients to the top three results on Google

Marketer

Marketing manager for local political candidate, responsible for establishing brand identity, communicating brand message, scheduling social media posts, managing social media advertising, designing website and landing pages, and directing video productions

Initiator

Started a Digital Marketing Agency in my free-time and learned that I'm not a salesman

Launched a Christian T-shirt brandand utilized an exclusive ambassador program to jump start brand awareness -- social media consistency and low profit margins limited its growth

Managed 25 person department overseeing \$800M+ of Government assets

Led 9-person cross-functional team to on-time award of \$450M production contract

Led \$17.5M test project with a 40 person team; developed a test operations schedule that challenged the status quo and saved \$700K and 3 weeks to the project

Communicator

Prepared a 4 year forecast for a \$1.3B pilot training system -- built relationships with vendors and end users to understand funding requirements and presented requirements to leadership to secure funding

Established communication and organizational standards across company for Asana, Slack, shared drives, and Microsoft Teams in order to maximize communication efficiency